http://www.summertreemosaics.com/legal/privacy-policy/

Introduction
This privacy policy (“Policy”) and this site’s Terms of Service (together the “Terms”) govern all use of http://www.summertreemosaics.com and that site’s services (together the “Site” or “Services”).
The owners and contributors to the Site will be referred to as “we,” “us,” or “our” in this Policy.
By using the Site or its Services, and/or by clicking anywhere on this Site to agree to the Terms and this Policy, you are deemed to be a “user” for purposes of this Policy.
You and every other user (“you” or “User” as applicable) are subject to this Policy.
You and each user also agree to the Terms by using the Services.
In these Terms, the word “Site” includes the site referenced above, its owner(s), contributors, suppliers, licensors, and other related parties.
We provide this privacy statement explaining our online information practices, so that you can decide whether and how to interact with the Site and the Services.
We may release your information when we deem it appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Please also review our Terms of Use section that governs the use and the users of the Site.
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. If we have your email address, we may also send an email notifying you of any changes.
Mobile Device Privacy
The following applies to our site, when viewed on a mobile device:
When accessed with a mobile deivce, our site may collect information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you have, device identifiers, and information about your use of the site. Regardless of the device you use to access the site, it will also collect information you provide, as well as information about your interaction with the site and its content.
If location services are activated on your mobile device, our site may collect information about the location of your device. Your mobile network service providers may collect device-specific information, such as a device identifier, when you use our website or one of our mobile applications. This information collected by your mobile network service will not be associated with your user account with us, or with your personally identifiable information.
Disputes
We are based in USA and you are contracting to use our Site.
This Policy and all matters arising from your use of the Site are governed by and will be construed according to the laws of USA, without regard to any choice of laws rules of any jurisdiction.
The federal courts and state courts that have geographical jurisdiction over disputes arising at our office location in USA will be the only permissible venues for any and all disputes arising out of or in connection with this Policy or the Site and Service.
No Users Under the Age of 13
The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13.
Children under the age of 13 should not use the Site at any time.
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.
If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected information from anyone under the age of 13, we will erase that information from our servers. It is a violation of our Terms of Service for children under the age of 13 to use the Site.
Terms Contact
If you have any questions about these Terms, please address them to admin@summertreemosaics.com.
Last Updated
These terms were last updated on December 19, 2015
It's only fair to share...FacebookTwitterPinterestLinkedin
Comments are closed.
Facebook
Advertisements
Recent Posts
Getting Real About Your Home Improvement Plans
Finding Ideas For Decorating Your Bathroom Tiles
Find A Modern Home Improvement Tool In Wall Decals
Easy Home Improvement Ideas To Really Make You Happy
Innovative Ideas for Waste Management That You Can Do at Home
CreativeApple updates Final Cut Pro X with social media tools, moreMarco Oggian's Dreams and Nightmares explores our global anxiety in 2020Ren & Stimpy returns in 'reimagined' formatApple updates the 27-inch iMac for 2020 with 10th-gen chips and a new screenThe first ever AR Pride floats come to Snapchat28 best picture books for children Announcement We’d like to thank Best Locksmith Brisbane for the quick solution to our lockout problem. You guys saved our vacation in Brisbane. For a reliable and fast solution to all your lock problems, visit https://bestlocksmithbrisbane.com.au
Legal PagesPrivacy Policy
Terms of Service
Designed by
Apollo Web Design LLC | Powered by
Wordpress
Pin It on Pinterest
